Finding Aid for the Augustus F. Hawkins papers LSC.1642
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Miscellaneous Material, 1963-90; (Contained in 11 Boxes)
  - Juanita Barbee Files, 1963-75
    - Public Relations
      - Political. (Box 98)
      - Thank You. (Box 98)
      - Questionnaire. (Box 98)
    - Hawkins Family Memorial Foundation
      - General. (Box 98)
      - Board Members. (Box 98)
      - Education Research Project, 1975. (Box 98)
    - Issues
      - Vietnam. (Box 98)
      - Miscellaneous. (Box 98)
      - Community Alert Patrol. (Box 98)
      - Adam Clayton Powell. (Box 98)
    - Defense Department, Miscellaneous. (Box 98)
    - A First Look at Emergency Employment Report. (Box 98)
  - Speeches, 1972-74
    - Full Employment Conference, Columbus, Ohio, November 1974. (Box 99)
    - RASSA Conference, Washington, D.C., October 1974. (Box 99)
    - Allegheny County Office of Economic Opportunity, October 1974. (Box 99)
    - Statement on Full Employment to President Ford, August 1974. (Box 99)
    - Urban League Convention, San Francisco, July 1974. (Box 99)
    - Reading Reform Foundation, Washington, D.C., May 1974. (Box 99)
    - Full Employment Conference, Columbia University, New York, March 1974. (Box 99)
    - Washington Technical Institute, re Influence of Congressional Black Conference, ca. 1974. (Box 99)
    - Negro Chamber of Commerce, Shreveport, Los Angeles, December 1973. (Box 99)
    - Remarks on Impeachment of President Nixon, November 1973. (Box 99)
    - Congressional Contact Workshop, ACSA Committee on Federal Legislation, November 1973. (Box 99)
    - Political Prisoners in South Vietnam, September 1973. (Box 99)
    - Black Superintendents' Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, July 1973. (Box 99)
    - Brownsville Hearing Statement, June 1973. (Box 99)
    - Recruitment and Training Program, Miami, Florida, March 1973. (Box 99)
    - Conference on Career Education, February 1973. (Box 99)
    - Indiana University re Afro-American Affairs, 1972. (Box 99)
  - Miscellaneous and To Be Filed
    - Publications and Books with Handwritten Notes. (Box 100)
    - Appointment Books, (2)., 1972-73 (Box 100)
    - Reagan and Civil Rights, 1983. (Box 100)
    - Japan, Australia, Singapore Trip, 1983. (Box 100)
    - AFL-CIO(?) Convention Speech. (Box 100)
    - Public Relations, Newsletter Comments, 1963. (Box 100)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1963-72. (Box 100)
    - Contributions, 1968-70. (Box 100)
    - Political, 1970-71. (Box 100)
    - Budget, 1981-83. (Box 100)
    - Congratulatory Letters on Re-election, 1964. (Box 100)
    - Campaign Expenses, 1964. (Box 100)
    - New Federalism and Health Manpower, 1973. (Box 100)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-80. (Box 100)
    - Press Files, 1977-90
      - Weekly Columns, Articles, Newsletters, Correspondence. (Box 101)
        - Augustus F. Hawkins with mail opposing Reagan Budget cuts, 1981 (Box 101)
    - Photographs, ca., 1975-90. (Box 101)
      - Augustus F. Hawkins, portrait, 1964 (Box 101)
      - Augustus F. Hawkins at press conference, 1985 (Box 101)
    - Photographs, ca., 1960-90. (Box 124)
    - Miscellaneous, ca., 1960-90. (Box 124)
    - A-V Tapes. (Box 134)
    - Education and Labor Committee Files
      - Susan Mcguire's (Staff Director) Files, 1985-90. (Box 139)
      - Miscellaneous Committee Files. (Box 139)
    - Photographs. (Box 139)
    - Minimum Wage Subject File, 1987-90. (Box 139)
    - Guestbooks, 1970-90. (Box 139)
    - Legislative Files--Gail Perry's Legal Assistant Files, 1984-90. (Box 139)
    - Index to Congressional Record Remarks, and Congressional Record Remarks, 1963-72 1973-84. (Box 139)